jrtstudio.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy | JRT Studio

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our sites, e-mail us directly or use any of our software. We collect anonymous analytics and we also collect crash reports without any personally identifiable data.

What information do we collect? 

E-Mail Address: When you enter your information, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Our Android applications never send us your email address. If we someday need your email address, we'll ask you for it.

Analytics: Our Android application may collect non-identifiable information from you using Google’s Firebase. This information includes things like how long you used the app for or which buttons you pressed.

IP Address: We do not collect your IP address, but this information is printed in the log files of our servers. The log files on the server are temporary and are generally overwritten in under twenty-four hours.

Crash Reports: We collect crash reports that show us where our code crashed. These reports contain information about the code, as well as device information like which operating system you are using and how much RAM was available at the time of the crash.

Ads: If you are viewing ads on Android, we may have Google Analytics Advertising Features on. This allows Google Analytics to show you more relevant ads, and allows us to see the demographics of our users. We do not sell or re-distribute this information. You can opt out of this advertising inside the "Google Settings" app on your device, if you want to.

Song Listening Information: Our Rocket Player and Songlytics application have features that backup your song listening information, such as how many times you’ve listened to a song, or what you’ve rated it. If you sign in with Google, this information is pseudo-anonymous. It would take extremely powerful computers a long time to figure out the song information is related to you. If you sign in using Spotify, this information can be directly tied to you.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience:
  * (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To store application data:
  * (your information helps us restore settings and backup useful information)
  * To improve our software:
  * (we continually strive to improve our software offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service:
  * (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

Who are our partners?

Facebook Audience Network. Facebook uses information it has collected to show you relevant ads. We have integrated Facebook’s code into our applications, but JRT Studio does not pass any information directly to Facebook. For information about Facebook and what it collects and how it uses your information, please refer to the following links.

[https://developers.facebook.com/docs/audience-network/policy/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://developers.facebook.com/docs/audience-network/policy/&sa=D&ust=1556325002387000)

[https://www.facebook.com/ads/manage/audience_network/publisher_tos/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.facebook.com/ads/manage/audience_network/publisher_tos/&sa=D&ust=1556325002388000)

MoPub. We use Twitter’s MoPub in our applications. MoPub’s privacy policy can be found here.

AdMob. Google’s AdMob is used. This is Google’s code, embedded in our applications. Google uses information it has collected outside of our app about you to provide personalized ads. We do not pass any of your personal information to Google. For more information from Google about what information it collects and how to control that information, please start at the following link.

Smaato. We use Smaato’s SDK in our applications in order to serve ads. We’ve been told by Smaato that their SDK only activates when an ad is requested and remains off if you are not seeing ads in our applications. Please view Smaato’s privacy policy at the following link.

AppLovin. We use AppLovin SDK in our applications in order to serve ads. We’ve been told by AppLocin that their SDK only activates when an ad is requested and remains off if you are not seeing ads in our applications.

Further, Google relies on a wide range of ad technology partners. We allow Google to use any partner they wish to use. For a full list of these partners, please view the following link.

Firebase. Google’s Firebase provides us with remote configuration of our app and analytics data. Their code is embedded is some of our applications. For a list of Google’s partners for Firebase, here is a link.

Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Your Consent

By using our site, or our software, you consent to our online privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at: info@jrtstudio.com
